[Music] I'm going to be robbed I'm going to be robbed I'm going to be robbed
I'm going to read this below is a danger loot.
Now if you guys have expressed it to me,
that area is a quality lot arrangement partner
and with that you get 208
and in that, whatever your
efficiency is in this car, you can get it made free of
cost and I can't mention this point
because the
insurance company charges 5%.
If we talk about the total amount, what was the expense on this, then
this upper point was
around Rs. 60 and this one from your lower
part is 100 rupees
and this side of the relationship, this Rahu
planet intake is also 50 rupees, so I'll
put the link in the description or apply it on the skin.
Now you can see what the price is, so
you can assume it's big, I've taken the lesson of surprising,
so this is a doctor body,
it's not more than six thousand, so let me
tell you, if  If you want to get a limit made
then you
can get it made by sending it to the workshop and you have to invest
Rs. 6000 in it and whatever
cost will be there, you will have to clear it and
if you want to track leaves
through half a kilo watt then
you can directly use the app and
claim the guarantee there
or you will call Ola and
after calling Ola you will have to tell
that you have gone home and you will have to
pay the money or along with this I will
bring the advisor to you in my pocket
what will he do, I will give you a platform,
you will fill the platform and you will get the vehicle
and after going to the workshop it will be made, it may take up to
a week
and then after that whatever invite will be
generated then you will have to pay that invoice,
after giving the demand problem
you will get this saree and you have to pay a
cancellation charge and the
money that you have in the same account will be refunded  It comes to
five percent and it
costs around one hundred rupees, it gives fibrosis
transmission, so this overall is
from my personal experience, the proof of which I have been able to
tell you all these things, okay, so
with this we can press it
and thanks so much for watching this
video file.